Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
- Box: 75, Folder: 2 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 23: Kroger Report of the Trustees, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    By Kroger Company. Employees' Profit Sharing and Retirement Income Program. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Kroger Management Benefit Program, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 25: Personnel Records Form, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 26: The Prudential Insurance Company of America SAMPLE Document, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 27: The Prudential Insurance Company of America SAMPLE Document, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 28: The Prudential Insurance Company of America SAMPLE Document, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 29: Operation Future: A Lifetime of Unlimited Horizons, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 30: Operation Future: A Lifetime of Unlimited Horizons, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 31: A Special Package of Protection for Members of Management, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 32: Additional Protection in Your Kroger Insurance Package for Regular Employees, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 33: Personal History of _____ Prepared for Kroger, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 34: Personal History of _____ Prepared for Kroger, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 35: The Kroger Co. Employment Application, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 36: Report of the Trustees 1957, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 37: Letter from John B. Hall President to Members of the Kroger-Profit Sharing Plan, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    By Kroger Company. February 14, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Personality: Ex-Track Star Hurdles Costs, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    By James J. Nagle. Sunday, January 6, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Investment Background: Kroger On the Move, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    By Louis J. Rolland. November 28, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Business Week: Bigger Store, Bigger, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 41: Performance Review Guide (Office Employee), Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 42: Salary Survey Comparisons, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 43: Job Questionnaire, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 44: Salary Survey Procedure, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 45: Kroger Employees' Profit Sharing and Retirement Income Program, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    By Kroger Company. June 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Summary of Clerical Rates and Fringe Benefits Survey, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 47: Employees' Retirement Program, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 48: Employees' Retirement Program, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 49: The Prudential Insurance Company of America, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 50: Kemba Mutual Insurance Association, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 51: How to use the "Improvement Guide" to Conduct a Performance Review Interview, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 52: Health and Accident Policy, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 53: Revised Employee Group Insurance Rules and Regulations, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 54: Declaration of Employer-Employee Relations Policies, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 55: A Message From, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 56: Kroger Foreman Improvement Guide, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 57: Pre-Retirement Interview Guide for Supervisory Employees conducting Pre-retirement interview, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 58: The Labor-Management Committee, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 59: Preliminary Application for Employment, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 60: Physical Examination, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 61: Fine Foods in the Making, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 62: Fine Foods in the Making, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 63: Kroger Inventory of Store Managers, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 64: Performance Review Guides for Store Employees, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 65: Prudential Insurance Company The Kroger Co., Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 66: Kemba Mutual Insurance Association, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 67: Index Kroger training programs, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 68: Kroger check your own safety "I.Q.", Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 69: Kroger, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    By J.A. Barron. Februrary 12, 1954, Kroger stationary, to Mr. J. Douglas Brown at Princeton University. Item is in English.
  - Item 70: Kroger Employee's Profit Sharing and Retirement Income program, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 71: Kroger Management Benefit Program, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 72: Kroger Employment Application, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 73: The Prudential Insurance Company of America The Kroger Co., Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    By Kroger Company. Yellow. Item is in English.
  - Item 74: the Prudential Insurance Company The Kroger Co., Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    By Kroger Company. orange. Item is in English.
  - Item 75: the Prudential Insurance Company The Kroger Co., Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 76: Operation Future a Lifetime of unlimited Horizons, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 77: Operation Future a Lifetime of unlimited Horizons, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Box: 75, Folder: 3 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Management Development Plan, Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Management Development Plan, Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
    By Kroger Company. Schedule B: For Frovery and Produce Management Trainees. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Sample Clerical Survey, Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: The Kroger Co.: Excerpts From The Kroger Plan For The Development of Men, Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Box: 75, Folder: 4 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Kroger Job Evaluation Plan, Publication (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Kroger Policy and Procedure Manual, Publication (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Box: 75, Folder: 5 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: 50th Anniversary, Publication (Box 75, Folder 5)
    By Kraft, Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Kraft Ink, Publication (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Box: 75, Folder: 6 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: An Employee Report on Monday Closings, Publication (Box 75, Folder 6)
    By L.S. Ayres & Co. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, Folder: 7 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Labor's Struggle for Freedom, Publication (Box 75, Folder 7)
    By Labor Chest. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, Folder: 8 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Labor Committee for Carey News, Publication (Box 75, Folder 8)
    By Labor Committee for Carey. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, Folder: 9 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Programs in Occupational Safety and Health for working men and women in Oregon, Publication (Box 75, Folder 9)
    By Labor Education and Research Center. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Workshop on Occupational Safety and Health for Women Workers, Publication (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: A Newsletter from LERC, Publication (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Occasional Notes, Publication (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Occasional Notes Bargaining Trends, Publication (Box 75, Folder 9)
- Box: 75, Folder: 10 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Quality of Medical Care, Publication (Box 75, Folder 10)
    By Labor Health Institute. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A union's experiment in Health Care, Publication (Box 75, Folder 10)
- Box: 75, Folder: 11 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: A Union's Experiment in Healthcare, Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: The Quality of Medical Care, Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
    By Franz Goldmann, Evarts A. Graham. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, Folder: 12 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Labor-Management Group Position Papers on Health care Costs, Publication (Box 75, Folder 12)
    By Labor Management Group. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, Folder: 13 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Employee Department and Labor Relations, Publication (Box 75, Folder 13)
    By LaSalle University. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, Folder: 14 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Municipal Revenues: Bits and Pieces, Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
    By Labor-Management Relations Service. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, Folder: 15 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Choices for American Industry, Publication (Box 75, Folder 15)
    By Marshall, Ray Glickman, Norman. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, Folder: 16 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: How to Avoid Unfair Labor Practices, Publication (Box 75, Folder 16)
    By Labor Relations Institute. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Practical Pointers on Incentive Plans, Publication (Box 75, Folder 16)
- Box: 75, Folder: 17 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Thrift Plan and Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 75, Folder 17)
    By Lago Oil & Transport Company, Ltd. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Survivor Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 75, Folder 17)
- Box: 75, Folder: 18 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Building of Men Through Multiple Management, Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
    By A.L. Bechtold. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, Folder: 19 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Office Employees' General Information, Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
    By J.D. Hackett. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, Folder: 20 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The Economics of Equality, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    By Tom Kahn. Two Copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: National Health Insurance, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    By Michael Davis. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Taft-Hartley Act in Action, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    By Jack Barbash. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Art of Pamphleteering, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    By League for Industrial Democracy. Example Pamplets Attached. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: L.I.D. Pamphlet Series, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    By League for Industrial Democracy. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: L.I.D. Pamphlets, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: L.I.D. Pamphlet Series, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Item 8: Recent Developments in the American Labor Movement, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    By Harry W. Laidler. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The L.I.D. and Its Activities, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Item 10: The L.I.D. and its Activities, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Item 11: The L.I.D. Advances, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    By League for Industrial Democracy. Attached Paper and Pamphlet. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Letter to Friend, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    By Tom Milstein. Letter with Attached Copy of Donor Form. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: New Growth for Democracy, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Item 14: LID News Bulletin, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
- Box: 75, Folder: 21 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: How Springfield Builds - Real Democracy, Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
    By The League for Fair Play, Inc. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, Folder: 22 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Two Proposed Statutes, Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
    By League for Industrial Rights. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Constitution, Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: A National Organization of Employers, Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
- Box: 75, Folder: 23 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: This is Lederle, Publication (Box 75, Folder 23)
    By Lederle. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, Folder: 24 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Safety Illustrated, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
    By Leeds and Northrup Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employees' Hand Book, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
- Box: 75, Folder: 25 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Mine Management Policies, Publication (Box 75, Folder 25)
    By Lehigh Coal and Navigation Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, Folder: 26 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Management Consultatns, Publication (Box 75, Folder 26)
    By Ewan Clague. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, Folder: 27 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Where Freedom Begins, Publication (Box 75, Folder 27)
    By Charles Luckman. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Civil War of 1947, Publication (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: Pension Plan, Publication (Box 75, Folder 27)
    By Lever Brothers. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, Folder: 28 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Management's Responsibility For Industrial Leadership, Publication (Box 75, Folder 28)
    By Sam Lewisohn. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, Folder: 29 (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Wanted - Improved Labor Leadership, Publication (Box 75, Folder 29)
    By William D. Rawlins. October 1935. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, Folder: 30 (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: A Message to Employers, Publication (Box 75, Folder 30)
    By Harold A. Ley. November 11, 1920. Item is in English.
- Box: 75, Folder: 31 (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Health Care Plan For Eligible Salaried Employees of Libbey-Owens-Ford Company, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
    By Libby-Owens-Ford. May 1, 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Health Care Plan For Eligible Hourly Employees of Libbey-Owens-Ford Co., Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
    By Libby-Owens-Ford. January 1, 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Hourly Employee Benefits for Eligible Hourly Employees of Libbey-Owens-Ford Co., Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 4: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
    By Libby-Owens-Ford. Revised 1-79. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Stephen W. Forbes of University of Illinois Namedd LOMA Vice President of Financial Planning and Control, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
    By Life Office Management Association. New York, NY; April 18, 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Nonexempt Employee Performance Appraisal Form, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
    By Libby-Owens-Ford. Revised: 6/79. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Nonexempt Employee Potential Appraisal Form (Condifential - Not to be Shown to Employee), Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
    By Libby- Owens-Ford. Revised: 6/79. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Exempt Employee Potential Appraisal Form (Confidential - Not to be Shown to Employee), Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 9: Exempt Employee Performance Appraisal Form, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 10: Glass for Construction, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
    By Libby-Owens-Ford. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Shield, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 12: The Shield, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 13: The Shield, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 14: The Shield, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 15: Group Insurance Coverage During Strikes, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 16: Memorandum Concerning the Arbitration Award in the Ottawa Issues, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 17: Supervisors and Labor Unions, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
    By Libby-Owens-Ford. Supervisors Bulletins, September 11. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Supervisors and Labor Unions, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
    By Libby-Owens-Ford. Supervisor's Bulletin, September 11. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: A Report on the Strike at Ottawa Plant August 3-7, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 20: Unionization of Office Employees, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 21: Group Insurance Coverage During Strikes, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 22: Memorandum Concerning the Charleston N.L.R.B.-Supervisor Case, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 23: Memorandum Concerning the Charleston N.L.R.B.-Supervisor Case, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 24: The Fundamental Facts of Production, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 25: The Understanding Foreman, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 26: Procedure for Establishing Wage Rates for New Operations or Changes in Method, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
    By Libby-Owens- Ford. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Maintaining Proper Human Relations, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
    By E.H. van Delden. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: The Wage and Hour Law as it Concerns Reporting Time in the Computation of Overtime for Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 29: Interpretation of Section 19, "Hours and Overtime", Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
    By E.H. van Delden. November 20. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: We of Libbey-Owens-Ford, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
- Box: 75, Folder: 32 (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Libby's Canned Foods, Publication (Box 75, Folder 32)
    By Libby, McNeill and Libby. This folder contains various small pamplets including reciepes, employee benefits, shopping in the computer age, among others. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Guide to Salad Artistry, Publication (Box 75, Folder 32)
    By Libby, McNeill and Libby. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Guide to Canned and Frozen Vegetables, Publication (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Item 4: Guide to Juices and Drinks, Publication (Box 75, Folder 32)
- Box: 76, Folder: 1 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Letter, Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    By M. B. Bradshaw. Labeled Separate Document #104; letter dated November 8, 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Application for Fidelity Bond, Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    By Liberty Mutual. Blank Application Form. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Humanics: A New Concept of Loss Control in Industry, Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    By Liberty Mutual. Copy withdrawn from Littauer Library. Item is in English.
- Box: 76, Folder: 2 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Saving The 'LB': Or, how Herkimer raised $6 million and kept 256 jobs in the Mohawk Valley, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    By Richard G. Case. Newspaper Article; October 30, 1977. Item is in English.
- Box: 76, Folder: 3 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: To Your Comfortable Old Age: An Explanation of the Rheingold Retirement Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
    By Personnel Services: Liebman Breweries. From Library NYSSILR. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: To Your Health and Welfare: An Explanation of the Rheingold Health and Welfare Program for Employees and Their Families, Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
- Box: 76, Folder: 4 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Long Term Disability Benefit Plan: Salaried Employees with Basic Earnings of at Least $7,500 Annually, Publication (Box 76, Folder 4)
    By Liggett and Myers Corp (Liggett Group). Handbooks, manuals, etc.; Published December, 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employees' Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 76, Folder 4)
    By Liggett and Myers Corp (Liggett Group). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Your Profit Sharing Plan, Publication (Box 76, Folder 4)
    By Liggett and Myers Corp (Liggett Group). Effective January 1, 1964; 1972 Edition. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: An Income for your Retirement Years: Salaried and Non-Bargaining Unit Employees, Publication (Box 76, Folder 4)
    By Liggett and Myers Corp (Liggett Group). Plan Arranged By: Marsh and McLennan Incorporated (Consulting Actuaries). Effective Date: January 1, 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Group Hospital and Medical Plan: Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 76, Folder 4)
    By Liggett and Myers Corp (Liggett Group). Effective December 1, 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: People make the difference at Liggett Group, Publication (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Performance Appraisal Form, Publication (Box 76, Folder 4)
    By Liggett and Myers Corp (Liggett Group). Contains guide to the use of the appraisal form; Blank appraisal form. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Performance Appraisal Form, Publication (Box 76, Folder 4)
    By Liggett and Myers Corp (Liggett Group). Blank Appraisal Form. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Companies of your Pleasure, Publication (Box 76, Folder 4)
    By Liggett and Myers Corp (Liggett Group). Also contains "The Products of your Pleasure". Item is in English.
- Box: 76, Folder: 5 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: your group insurance, Publication (Box 76, Folder 5)
    By Eli Lilly and Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Military-Service Policy, Publication (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: In The War, Publication (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Your Group Insurance, Publication (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Spot News, Publication (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: When You Retire, Publication (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Employment Policy, Publication (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Suggestion system, Publication (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: on the job with lilly, Publication (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Excerpts From Employment Department Manual, Publication (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: On the Job With Lilly, Publication (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Articles of Incorporation and Bylaws of the Eli Lilly Credit Union, Publication (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: The Lilly Review, Publication (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: The Lilly Review, Publication (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Organization Charts, Publication (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Box: 76, Folder: 6 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Lilly Management Procedures Manual, Publication (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Box: 76, Folder: 7 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Retirement Annuity Plan, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Articles of Agreement and Certificate of Organization, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Absence Report, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Progress Record, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Careers with Lilly, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: General Organization, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Your Group Insurance, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Organization Chart, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Merit Increase Program, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Personal History Record, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Industrial Relations Section, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Organizational Directory, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Training Programs, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Personnel Test, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: Personnel Test, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Progress Record, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: Specific Safety Instructions for Label Supply Department, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: Management Report, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 19: The Lilly Review, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 20: Checklist of Material Needed on Company, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 21: Decentralizing the Staff Personnel Function, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 22: Poster, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 23: Lilly Library, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 24: New Grievance Plan, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 25: Returiung War Veterans, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 26: Credit Union, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 27: The Division Representatives Group of Eli Lilly, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 28: The Lilly Military Policy, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 29: Industrial Relations Section, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 30: To all employees:, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 31: To all employees:, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 32: Industrial Relations Section, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 33: Industrial Relations Section, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 34: Industrial Relations Section, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 35: Nutrition Work in Industry, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)